import { Flashcard } from "../types";

export const southAmericanCapitals: Flashcard[] = [
    { front: "Argentina", back: "Buenos Aires" },
    { front: "Bolivia", back: "UPDATE" },
    { front: "Brazil", back: "Brasilia" },
    { front: "Chile", back: "Santiago" },
    { front: "Colombia", back: "Bogota" },
    { front: "Ecuador", back: "Quito" },
    { front: "Guyana", back: "Georgetown" },
    { front: "Paraguay", back: "Asuncion" },
    { front: "Peru", back: "Lima" },
    { front: "Suriname", back: "Paramaribo" },
    { front: "Uruguay", back: "Montevideo" },
    { front: "Venezuela", back: "Caracas" }
];